[{"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 2}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [2, 9, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 3}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [3, 8, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 3}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [3, 9, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 4}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [4, 7, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 4}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [4, 8, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 4}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [4, 9, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 5}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 6}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [5, 6, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 5}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [5, 7, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 5}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [5, 8, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 5}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [5, 9, 14], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 6}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 5}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [6, 5, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 6}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 6}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [6, 6, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 6}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [6, 7, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 6}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [6, 8, 14], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 6}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [6, 9, 15], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 4}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 4, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 5}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 5, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 6}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 6, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 7, 14], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 8, 15], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 7}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [7, 9, 16], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 3}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 3, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 4}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 4, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 5}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 5, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 6}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 6, 14], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 7, 15], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 8, 16], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 8}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [8, 9, 17], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 2}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 2, 11], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 3}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 3, 12], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 4}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 4, 13], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 5}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 5, 14], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 6}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 6, 15], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 7}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 7, 16], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 8}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 8, 17], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}, {"body": [{"type": "au-add-up2", "stem": "看图列算式，原来有多少", "unit": "个", "name": "篮球", "show": {"img": "sphere_items/ff2b0783e751a9388728a960d16ef998.svg", "num": 9}, "tips": {"img": "people_head_boy/1286eb2d0fa94d0b7583c3af55643ac1.svg", "num": 9}, "equation": ["", "+", "", "=", ""]}], "answers": [9, 9, 18], "explain": "", "knowledges": ["20以内进位加法应用"], "type": "填空", "level": "1", "number": "1-7-9-09"}]